The snow glows white on the mountain tonight,
Not a footprint to be seen.
A kingdom of isolation and it looks like I’m the queen.
The wind is howling like this swirling storm inside.
Couldn’t keep it in; Heaven knows I tried.
Don’t let them in, don’t let them see.
Be the good girl you always have to be.
Conceal, don’t feel, don’t let them know.
Well, now they know.
Let it go, let it go
Can’t hold it back anymore
Turn away and slam the door
I don't care what they're going to say.
Let the storm rage on.
The cold never bothered me anyway.
It's funny how some distance,
makes everything seem small.
And the fears that once controlled me, can't get to me at all
It's time to see what I can do,
to test the limits and break through.
No right, no wrong, no rules for me.
I'm free!
Let it go, let it go.
I am one with the wind and sky.
You'll never see me cry.
Here l stand, and here I'll stay.
Let the storm rage on.
My power flurries through the air into the ground.
My soul is spiraling in frozen fractals all around
And one thought crystallizes like an icy blast
I'm never going back; the past is in the past!
Let it go, let it go.
And I'll rise like the break of dawn.
Let it go, let it go
That perfect girl is gone
Here I stand, in the light of day
Let the storm rage on
The cold never bothered me anyway
Hi! Thanks for watching this video!
We would like to give a special shoutout to Powder Mountain Ski Resort
You can check out their website here
They've got some awesome family deals and they have really good snow and their staff is really super awesome so you shall go ski there
Also, you can follow us on Facebook and Twitter and Instagram, and you can subscribe here, to see more videos!
Anna, for your birthday, I've got you a shirt to remind you to never mary a man with fake sideburns.
Can't mary man with fake sideburns
Can't mary a man with fake sideburns.
Oh! Hello there!
AAHH!
Can't mary a man with fake sideburns